A Guide to the Old Dominion University Photograph Collection 1930s-1990s
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- 1950s
  - Student Organizations-Beaux Art Club (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Student Organizations-Business and Economics Club (I) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Student Organizations-Business and Economics Club (II) (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Student Organizations-Canterbury Association (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Student Organizations-Circle K Club (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Student Organizations-Cotillion (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Omega Phi (I) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Omega Phi (II) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Omega Phi (III) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Phi Omega (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Sigma Lambda (I) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Student Organizations-Delta Sigma Lambda (II) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Student Organizations-Di Gamma (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Student Organizations-English Club (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Student Organizations-Evening College Club (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Student Organizations-Gamma Gamma (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Student Organizations-Gavel Club (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Student Organizations-German Club (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Student Organizations-History Club (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Student Organizations-IMPS (I) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Student Organizations-IMPS (II) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Student Organizations-International Club (I) (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Student Organizations-International Club (II) (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Student Organizations-International Club (III) (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Student Organizations-Inter-varsity (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Student Organizations-Kappa Kappa Kappa (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Student Organizations-Kappa Sigma Kappa (I) (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Student Organizations-Kappa Sigma Kappa (II) (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Student Organizations-Methodist Student Movement (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Student Organizations-Modern Dance Club (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Student Organizations-Monogram Club (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Student Organizations-Newman Club (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Student Organizations-Phalanx Club (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Student Organizations-Phi Theta Kappa (I) (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Student Organizations-Phi Theta Kappa (II) (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Student Organizations-Pi Phi Sigma (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Student Organizations-Political Club (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Student Organizations-Professional Businessmen's Club (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Student Organizations-Sigma Alpha Iota (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Student Organizations-Sigma Beta Tau (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Student Organizations-Sigma Delta Phi (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Student Organizations-Sigma Epsilon Pi (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (I) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (II) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (III) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (IV) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (V) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (VI) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (VII) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Student Organizations-Student Government (VIII) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Student Organizations-Student Wives Club (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Student Organizations-Synchronized Swimming Club (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Student Organizations-Theta Mu Chi (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Student Organizations-Tiga (I) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Student Organizations-Tiga (II) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Student Organizations-Tiga (III) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Student Organizations-United Nations Collegiate Chapter (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Student Organizations-Veteran's Club (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Student Organizations-Virginia Epsylon (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Student Organizations-Wesley Foundation (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Student Portraits, 33 Folders (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 1-Box 25, Folder 17:)
  - Traditional Events-Careers Program (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Traditional Events-Christmas Tree (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I) (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II) (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I), 1951-1953 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II), 1951-1953 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I), 1954-1955 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II), 1954-1955 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I), 1956-1957 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II), 1956-1957 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (III), 1956-1957 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (IV), 1956-1957 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I), 1957 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II), 1957 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I), 1958 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II), 1958 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (III), 1958 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (IV), 1958 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (I), 1959 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Traditional Events-Graduation (II), 1959 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Traditional Events-Homecoming, 1955-1959 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 21)
- 1960s
  - Alumni (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Activities (I) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Activities (II) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Activities (III) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Activities (IV) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Activities (V) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Activities (VI) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Activities (VII) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Activities (VIII) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Convocations (I) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Convocations (II) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Convocations (III) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Convocations (IV) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Convocations (V) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Convocations (VI) (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Honors and Awards (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Honors and Awards, 1960-1961 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Honors and Awards (I), 1962-1963 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Honors and Awards (II), 1962-1963 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Honors and Awards (I), 1964 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Honors and Awards (II), 1964 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Honors and Awards (I), 1965 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Honors and Awards (II), 1965 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Honors and Awards (I), 1966-1968 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Honors and Awards (II), 1966-1968 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (I) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (II) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (III) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous (IV) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Non-Academic Staff (I) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Non-Academic Staff (II) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Non-Academic Staff (III) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Non-Academic Staff (IV) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Non-Academic Staff (V) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Non-Academic Staff (VI) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Non-Academic Staff (VII) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Non-Academic Staff (VIII) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Politicians (I) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Politicians (II) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Politicians (III) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Theater (I) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Theater (II) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Theater (III) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Theater (IV) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Theater (V) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Theater (VI) (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Theater-"Andromache" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Theater-"Antigone" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Theater-"The Apollo of Bellac" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Theater-"Aria Da Capo" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Theater-"Curse You Jack Dalto" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Theater-"The Debutantes" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Theater-"The Emperor's New Clothes" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Theater-"Isle" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Theater-"Jumping Frog" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Theater-"The Lady of Larkspur" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Theater-"The Matchmaker" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Theater-"No Exit" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Theater-"Passion, Poison, and Petrafaction" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Theater-"Rashoman" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Theater-"You Can't Take It With You" (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 24)
  - University Administration (I) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 1)
  - University Administration (II) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 2)
  - University Administration (III) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 3)
  - University Administration (IV) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 4)
  - University Administration (V) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 5)
  - University Administration (VI) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 6)
  - University Administration (VII) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 7)
  - University Administration (VIII) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 8)
  - University Administration (IX) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 9)
  - University Administration (X) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 10)
  - University Administration (XI) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 11)
  - University Administration (XII) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 12)
  - University Administration (XIII) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 13)
  - University Administration (XIV) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 14)
  - University Administration (XV) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Academic Departments-Art (I) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Academic Departments-Art (II) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Academic Departments-Art (III) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Academic Departments-Biology (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Academic Departments-School of Business (I) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Academic Departments-School of Business (II) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Academic Departments-Chemistry (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Academic Departments-Child Study Center (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Academic Departments-Division of Continuing Education (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Academic Departments-Division of Technology: Dental (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Academic Departments-School of Education (I) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Academic Departments-School of Education (II) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Academic Departments-School of Education (III) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Academic Departments-School of Education (IV) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Academic Departments-School of Engineering (I) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Academic Departments-School of Engineering (II) (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Academic Departments-English (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Academic Departments-English (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Academic Departments-Foreign Languages (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Academic Departments-Geology (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Academic Departments-History (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Academic Departments-Industrial Arts (I) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Academic Departments-Industrial Arts (II) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Academic Departments-Industrial Arts (III) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Academic Departments-Math (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Academic Departments-Music (I) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Academic Departments-Music (II) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Academic Departments-Music (III) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Academic Departments-Music (IV) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Academic Departments-Music (V) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Academic Departments-Music (VI) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Academic Departments-Music (VII) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Academic Departments-Music (VIII) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Academic Departments-Nursing (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Academic Departments-Oceanography (I) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Academic Departments-Oceanography (II) (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Academic Departments-Philosophy (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (I) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (II) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (III) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (IV) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (V) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Academic Departments-Physical Education (VI) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Academic Departments-Physics (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Academic Departments-Psychology (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Academic Departments-School of Education (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Academic Departments-School of Sciences (I) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Academic Departments-School of Sciences (II) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Academic Departments-School of Sciences (III) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Academic Departments-Sociology (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Academic Departments-Speech (I) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Academic Departments-Speech (II) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Academic Departments-Speech and Hearing Center (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (I) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (II) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (II) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Academic Departments-Technical Institute (WMTI)(III) (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Athletics-Baseball (I) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Athletics-Baseball (II) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Athletics-Baseball (III) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Athletics-Baseball (IV) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Athletics-Baseball (V) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Athletics-Basketball (I) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Athletics-Basketball (II) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Athletics-Basketball (III) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Athletics-Cheerleaders (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Athletics-Golf (I) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Athletics-Golf (II) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Athletics-Golf, Women's (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Athletics-Gymnastics (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Athletics-Gymnastics, Women's (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Athletics-Field Hockey (I) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Athletics-Field Hockey (II) (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Athletics-Football (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Athletics-Swimming (I) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Athletics-Swimming (II) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Athletics-Swimming (III) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Athletics-Swimming (IV) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Athletics-Team Captains (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Athletics-Tennis (I) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Athletics-Tennis (II) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Athletics-Tennis (III) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Athletics-Tennis, Women's (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Athletics-Track (I) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Athletics-Track (II) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Athletics-Track (III) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Athletics-Track (IV) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Athletics-Track (V) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Athletics-Track (VI) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Athletics-Wrestling (I) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Athletics-Wrestling (II) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Athletics-Wrestling (III) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Athletics-Wrestling (IV) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Athletics-Wrestling (V) (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Buildings and Grounds (I) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds (II) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds (III) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds (IV) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds (V) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VI)(Local Area Map Included) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VII) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds (VIII) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds (XIX) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds (X) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds (XI) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds (XII) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds (XIII) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Administration (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Chandler Hall (I) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Chandler Hall (II) (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Chemistry (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Child Study Center (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Dormitories (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Education (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Engineering (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Engineering Laboratory (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Fieldhouse (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Fine Arts (I) (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Fine Arts (II) (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Fine Arts (III) (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Foreman Field (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (I) (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hughes Library (II) (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Maintenance Building (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds-New Science Building (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Old Science Building (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Social Studies Building (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Technical Institute (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Webb Center (I) (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Webb Center (II) (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Webb Center (III) (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 19)
  - The Dance (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 1)
  - The Dance-American Ballet Theater (I) (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 2)
  - The Dance-American Ballet Theater (II) (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 3)
  - The Dance-American Ballet Theater (III) (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 4)
  - The Dance-Harkness Ballet (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 5)
  - The Dance-O.D.U. Ballet (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 6)
  - The Dance-The Royal Winnipeg Ballet (I) (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 7)
  - The Dance-The Royal Winnipeg Ballet (II) (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 8)
  - The Dance-The Royal Winnipeg Ballet (III) (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Faculty, 55 Folders (Box-folder Box 38, Folder 10-Box 41, Folder 13:)
  - Faculty Activities (I) (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Activities (II) (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Activities (III) (Box-folder Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Musical Performances (I) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Musical Performances (II) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Musical Performances (III) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Musical Performances (IV) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Musical Performances (V) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Musical Performances-Victoria De LosAngeles (I) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Musical Performances-Victoria De LosAngeles (II) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Musical Performances-Shmuel Ashkenasi (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Musical Performances-Gina Bachauer (I) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Musical Performances-Gina Bachauer (II) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Musical Performances-Gina Bachauer (III) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Musical Performances-John Browning (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Musical Performances-"Cavlleria Rusticana" (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Musical Performances-Van Cliburn (I) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Musical Performances-Van Cliburn (II) (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Musical Performances-"The Devil and Daniel Webster" (Box-folder Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Musical Performances-"The Fantastics" (I), 1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Musical Performances-"The Fantastics" (II), 1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Musical Performances-Eileen Farrell (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Musical Performances-Al Hirt, 1969 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Musical Performances-"Marat-Sade," 1969 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Musical Performances-Marlboro Quartet (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Musical Performances-"Marriage of Figaro," 1968 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Musical Performances-"The Music Man," 1969 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Musical Performances-Wilson Pickett (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Musical Performances-"South Pacific" (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Musical Performances-The Vienna Johann Straus Orchestra (I) (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Musical Performances-The Vienna Johann Straus Orchestra (II) (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Musical Performances-The Vienna Johann Straus Orchestra (III) (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Musical Performances-Jurg Von Vintschger (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Other Events-American Association of University Professors (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Other Events-Azalea Festival (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Other Events-Career Day (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Other Events-DECA Convention in Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1969 (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Chandler Hall (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Chemistry Building (I) (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Chemistry Building (II) (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Fine Arts Building (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Gresham Hall (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Hughes Library (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Kaufman Hall (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Webb Center (I) (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Webb Center (II) (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Other Events-Dedication: Webb Center (III) (Box-folder Box 43, Folder 27)